veer.tv 2018-10-01

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy (the “ ​Statement​ ”) describes the policies and procedures regarding the collection,
use, and disclosure of personal information received through the VeeR Service, including but not limited
to our websites and other applications (the “ ​Site​ ”). The terms “ ​we​ ”, “ ​us​ ”, “ ​our​ ”, “ ​VeeR​” , and “
Service​ ” refer to the VeeR Service. The terms “ ​you​ ”, “ ​your​ ”, and “ ​users​ ” refer to visitors, registered
users, and all other users of the Service. By accessing or using the Service, you are consenting to our
processing of your information as set forth in this Statement now and as amended by us. You
acknowledge that this Statement is part of our ​Terms of Service​ . Please do not access or use the
Service if you are unwilling or unable to be bound by the Terms of Service and the Privacy Policy.
1.INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT
Personal Information. ​If you create an account to take advantage of the full range of services offered on
the Site, we ask for and store account information that can be used to identify or contact you (“ ​Personal
Information​ ”), such as your email address. You can also import your account information from a third
party. We may use this Personal Information to expedite your registration process, and enhance and
customize your experience on the Site. Your Personal Information will not be visible to other users. You
can update or change your Personal Information at any time via your account settings. Also, When the
user logs in through the third party, and authorizes VeeR to obtain the user contact information from third
party, it means that the user agrees to authorize VeeR team to send messages to the contact. Messages
include but not limited to system messages, activity push, content recommendation and other email
messages.
Public Content. Y  ​ ou can contribute to and interact with the Site in a number of different ways, including
but not limited to filling out your account information, creating channels and filling out your channel
profiles, uploading videos, creating playlists, liking and disliking content, commenting on content, and
subscribing to channels. We may store these contributions and interactions (your “ ​Public Content​” ),
display them to other Site visitors and users, and use them for promotional purposes. Note that any
information you provide in your channel profiles, including your channel names and avatars, is visible to
the public. Please do not include information in your Public Content that you expect to keep private. We
are not liable or responsible for the information you choose to include in your Public Content.
Inviting friends. ​You may choose to invite your friends to join VeeR by providing their contact information
or by importing your connections from other websites. We may store and use your friends’ contact
information for the sole purpose of allowing you to invite them to join and connect with you on the Site.
Activity and log data. ​We automatically store information related to your use of the Site (“ ​Activity​ ”), such
as the pages you view on the Site, your browser type and language, Internet Protocol address, requested
URL, referring URL, and the date and time of your visit. We use this type of information to administer the
Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the
aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest
in and use of the various areas of the Site.

Location data. ​When you use the Site, we may collect and use your approximate physical location (based
on the Internet Protocol address of your computer or your current location from your mobile device,
should you choose to provide it) to offer you tailored content - like giving you more relevant search results
, location based informations and ads.
Cookies. ​We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the
quality of our service. “ ​Cookies​ ” refer to small pieces of information that a website sends to your
computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Site. We may use both session cookies (which expire
once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them).
Persistent cookies can be removed by following the instructions in your browser’s help menu. If you
choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all.
Third party services. ​We allow you to access third party services, such as Facebook and Twitter, to share
your selected Public Content with those services, and import information about who you are connected
with on those services so that you can connect with people you know on the Site. You can manage your
third party services preferences at any time via your VeeR settings. Some third party services may also
provide us with information from your accounts on these services that allows us to enhance and
customize your experience on the Site. You can also further modify your privacy settings with third party
services directly.
Feedback. I​ f you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we may store
your communications, including any Personal Information you include in them, so that we can effectively
respond to you. Our contact information is provided at the end of this Statement.
Administration. W ​ e may use the information described above for routine administrative purposes, such as
investigating abuses on the Site, responding to user inquiries, and enforcing and applying our Terms of
Service and this Statement.
Credit card purchases. ​If you purchase products and services through VeeR, we may collect and store
billing and credit card information. This information will only be shared with third parties who perform
tasks (such as fulfilling orders and processing credit card payments) required to complete the purchase
transaction. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our registration or
order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology.
2. TRANSFER OF INFORMATION
Public Content. ​We may distribute your Public Content to third parties with your permission or pursuant to
our Terms of Service. For example, if you post content on the Site, we may distribute such Public Content
to a wider audience by sharing it (or portions of it) with third parties so that they can publish it on their own
websites and media platforms. When we distribute your Public Content to third parties, we may ask them
to credit you as the source of these contributions by including your display name and profile image.
Third party service providers. W ​ e provide some of our services through contractual agreements with
affiliates, partners, service providers, and other third parties. We may share information about you with
our service providers so that they can perform the services they are required to perform. Our service

providers are not permitted to use your Personal Information other than to provide those requested
services. We will encourage our service providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of
your Personal Information by our service providers is governed by the privacy policies of these service
providers, and is not subject to our control.
Third party advertising. W    ​ e may use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit VeeR.
These companies may use information from your Public Content (not including your Personal Information)
and Activity related to your use of the Site to provide advertisements about goods and services that may
be of interest to you. We do not send any individualized Personal Information to third party advertisers,
but these advertisers may have access to information that they obtain through Cookies or that you share
with these advertisers yourself. Note that we do not rent, share, sell, or trade your personally identifiable
information with third parties for direct marketing purposes.
Aggregate information. ​We may share non​personal information in the aggregate to third parties relating to
user behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationship with those third parties, such
as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have
been exposed to or clicked on advertising banners.
Business transfers. W    ​ e may share your information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures,
or other companies under a common control that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will
require them to honor this Statement. If another company acquires our company or all or substantially all
of our assets, that company will possess your information, and will assume the rights and obligations with
respect to that information as described in this Statement.
Investigations. W  ​ e reserve the right to investigate abuses on the Site, and to enforce and apply our Terms
of Service and this Statement. We may disclose information about you to third parties if we have a good
faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) take action regarding suspected illegal
activities; (ii) enforce or apply our Terms of Service and this Statement; (iii) comply with legal process or
other government inquiry, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal
process served on us; or (iv) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or
the public.
3. MANAGING YOUR INFORMATION
You can access、change and delete your Personal Information at any time via your account settings or
by contacting us with your request at support [at] VeeR [dot] com. ​ You also can contact with VeeR’s
DPO(data protection officer ) Richard Chen, who is incharge of whole data protection, by sending email to dpo[at]
VeeR [dot] com, or calling 010-53684521. VeeR team already set up the company ​Data Safety Monitoring
Committee, ​ to protect user data security. And Accounts may be deleted from the VeeR Service if they remain
inactive (i.e. the user fails to log in) for a continuous period of at least six (6) months.
We use your email address to send you notifications, newsletters, and updates. You can access and
change your email preferences at any time via your account settings or by contacting us at support [at]
VeeR [dot] com. However, despite your indicated email preferences, we may still need to contact you as
required by law or on legal matters, for example to inform you of any material updates to our Terms of
Service or this Statement.

4. SECURITY
Your account is password protected. Your password will never be visible to employees or affiliates of
VeeR.
We follow generally accepted industry standards to safeguard against the loss, misuse, and alteration of
your Personal Information, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission
over the Internet or method of electronic storage is fully secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to
use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its
absolute security.
We will make any legally​ required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of
your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Information to you via email or conspicuous posting on
the Site and will do so without unreasonable delay.
5. LINKS
The Site may contain links to third party websites with which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth
herein, we do not share your Personal Information with those third parties, and are not responsible for
their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies of all such third party websites.
6. OUR POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN
The Site is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly
collect Personal Information from children under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us
with Personal Information without your consent, please contact us at support [at] VeeR [dot] com. If we
become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information without parental consent,
we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.
7. MODIFICATIONS TO THIS STATEMENT
We may revise this Statement from time to time. The most current version of this Statement will govern
our use of your information and will always be located here. If we make a change to this Statement that
we believe materially reduces your rights, we may post a notice of such changes prior to implementing
them on the Site and/or email you at the email address associated with your account.
You acknowledge and agree to maintain a valid email address as a registered user, review the Site and
this Statement periodically, and remain aware of any modifications to this Statement. By continuing to
access or use the Service after any changes to this Statement become effective, you agree to be bound
by the revised Statement.
8. CONTACT
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of VeeR, you
can email us at support [at] VeeR [dot] com.
